This guy, Ed Blum, that got affirmative action overturned, he also went after some law firms for their diversity programs.
Of course he sued us, but what he's trying to do is eliminate any race-conscious decision-making in America.
So let me tell you what that means for all of us.
Who in this room went to an HBCU? We went to FAMU.
Okay, all right, okay, so if he's successful, there may be no HBCUs.
Because of Ed Blum and his organization, the SBA stopped their 8A program.
So anybody, a minority, sort of certified business, if he's successful, that won't exist anymore.
So companies won't be able to come to you and say, yes, we want to partner with you because you're a black-owned business,
or yes, we want to partner with you because you're a woman.
If you've ever been through a leadership development program that helped high-potential, underrepresented folks, black and brown people,
he's trying to eliminate all of that.
If you've got contracts, NIL deals, if you're an athlete, he's coming after that.
If you're in media or entertainment.
So that's why I often tell people you might see the news about Fearless Fund and think, oh, that's too bad for those black women.
He's coming for all of us.
He's coming for everything black, and we must fight back, and we must stand up.
Thank you.